<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>messenger on adenosinetp10</title><link>http://adenosinetp10.github.io/tags/messenger/</link><description>Recent content in messenger on adenosinetp10</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 19:01:07 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://adenosinetp10.github.io/tags/messenger/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Why I Use Telegram</title><link>http://adenosinetp10.github.io/posts/why-i-use-telegram/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 19:01:07 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://adenosinetp10.github.io/posts/why-i-use-telegram/</guid><description>Here I talk about how I came to know about telegram and why I continued to use it as my daily instant messaging app.</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2 id="telegram"><code>Telegram</code></h2>
<p>For those who has never heard of this word, let me tell you what it is. <a href="https://telegram.org">Telegram Messenger</a> which in short is called &lsquo;Telegram&rsquo; is an internet instant messaging app.</p>
<p>
  <img loading="lazy" src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/8/83/Telegram_2019_Logo.svg/121px-Telegram_2019_Logo.svg.png" alt="Telegram 2019 Logo.svg"  /></p>
<p>One could talk to their contacts through Telegram if they also happen to have that app. One could create/join groups, channels where they could chat with others and share anything. So, basically it&rsquo;s pretty much like any other instant messaging app.</p>
<h3 id="how-i-came-to-know-about-telegram">How I came to know about Telegram</h3>
<p>Like, how every tale goes, once upon a time, I was very bored and all I had at the moment was my dad&rsquo;s android smartphone with me in the house. I used to play games like Subway Surfers, Temple Run, Angry Birds, Clash of Clans and so on&hellip; In a word, It was the golden era for android games 🔥 where you could find quality games. I was going through the Google Play Store looking for something to download. This is where I got recommended to download this app called &ldquo;Telegram&rdquo;. I knew it was an instant messaging app, but never used it before. I assumed it would be similar to Facebook/Whatsapp, so downloaded it to check out what it&rsquo;s all about.</p>
<h3 id="first-time-experience">First time Experience</h3>
<p>Ok, so I have downloaded the app</p>
]]></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>